The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
The Black Bulls traveled to Rockway for trading,
hoping to fortify their magic skills.
There, Asta and Noel reunited with Kahono and Kieto
and were called upon to solve a problem
that was brewing under the waves.
A guardian of the sea had gone on a rampage,
posing a deadly threat to the people of the Underwater Temple.
Noelle and a few of the others took to the water to quell the chaos.
I'll keep getting stronger, Mom. Watch me. I'm just getting started.
But, Noel wasn't the only member of the Black Bulls who had vowed to become stronger.
What is this?
Apparently these foods are supposed to explosively enhance mana.
Sounds interesting. I didn't know you could make food like that.
Alright, down the hatch.
Not sure what you expect to happen since you don't have any magic.
I don't know! Maybe it'll make my anti-magic better somehow!
It's worth a try, right?
Time to dig in!
Oof
Whoa! It feels like it's already working!
Yeah, my mana is flowing like a waterfall!
What the hell's going on?!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!
This is some powerful sauce, man!
Leave me there, you guys!
I wonder what was in that food.
Oh, no, it's all three of them!
Hey! Charmy, do something!
Somebody's gonna get hurt!
That food wasn't good enough.
You guys chill, you'll rush out!
I know. I'll go see him.
Oh, no, it's all three of them!
Yeah, yeah!
強く風吹く世界の果てで
僕らは今日も目を閉じる夢を見る飽きもせず
今は小さく儚い希望も
いつか時代を変えてゆく光になると信じて
背負うべきものなど何一つないさ
全て抱きしめてゆく
たとえばそれが痛みだとしても
叶うなら君と共に
この声がこの喉が振り切れるほど
今叫ぶよ
未来は自分で切り開くんだって
とめとなく溢れ出る情熱のままさ
歩き出そう
To fill my dream
ご視聴ありがとうございました
You want me to train you?
ねぇ
消せPCON
消費
That allows me to cook meals that recover a person's mana.
But that isn't enough!
I need to whip up something that'll kick my friend's magic into overdrive!
Ah, I see. That's not going to be an easy task.
Hope you're ready to work hard, Shortcake.
You know it!
986! 987!
These sheep cooks are your magic.
But you can't simply work on making them stronger.
That isn't going to give you the result you're after.
The only way to make that happen is to put aside your magic
and concentrate on training beyond your physical limits
so you and the sheep cooks will have what it takes
to create the food that can enhance mana.
99!
1!
1000!
Your stamina's much better.
According to this book,
the next thing you need to do is gather some unknown ingredients.
Three items so rare, even I've never seen them.
That's pretty vague, but leave it to me, sir.
First, we need the bulb of a Mentan Pin Mandoradora.
Got it!
Next, hunt down the no one's heard of this coelacanth.
And lastly, the butt hide of a surprise Squatch.
Give me your butt fluff!
Shortcake did what?
Are you kidding me?
It's her!
Why did you push that hard?
Master!
I did what you said, and now…
My Charmy Papitsen will create the most powerful mana-enhancing dishes that have ever existed in this world.
Tonight, I'll cook up a feast for all my friends.
So whatever this is, it'll enhance everyone's mana.
Um, why do I have to be a part of this?
Because we need an escape plan if things go south.
Wait, what's gonna go south?
Charmy must have worked really hard to make this food.
Eat it!
You know what? I'm stuffed.
Yeah, I'm not hungry.
We should go. Thanks, Charmy.
Guys, please, we have to eat it!
We gotta show Charmy that she didn't do all of this for no reason!
I beg you to stay!
This meal was made by the shi-
No, Charmy, after she risked her life to obtain the ingredients to enhance her friend's magic!
Wait, who the heck is this guy?
Master!
I'll stop!
You see that? Demon food!
I don't think you cooked this enough!
Don't worry! Spatial magic, Fallen Angel Gate!
What are you bozos doing?
Captain Yummy?
You better not be running off with my wheels. What if I need to go to the bathroom?
Sorry, sir, but you just have to hold it in!
Huh?
That looks bad.
I knew it! It's demon food!
No, not demon food!
You just made that up, didn't you?
Why don't you cut the crap and be straight with us?
Is that someone we know, or...?
I've never seen it firsthand, but legend has it a massive amount of mana combined with the love of a devoted friend can cause food to come to life!
It absolutely can't!
No? Then how else would you explain what's happening?
Charlie's desire to improve her squadmate's magic power was as pure and genuine as it gets!
That's how the food she made ended up so jam-packed with mana!
There was nothing else that could have caused it!
My food's an evil monster?
Hey, are you okay?
Oh man, it's got me!
Magna!
I don't know why, but my body feels really weak now.
Look!
It's draining away our mana.
How is this even possible?
That's what makes demon food such a deadly threat!
It absorbs mana from everyone in the vicinity until it becomes unstoppable!
No, really, who are you?
I worked so hard on those noms!
Hey kid! Quit daydreaming already!
That thing is using mana and you've got an anti-magic sword!
Do you need me to spell it out for you?
It's just that...
Fine.
Guess I'll take care of it.
I'd like to think I could count on my squad to clean up their own messes, but here we are!
No, don't!
Huh?
You wanna explain yourself?
Captain, we can't just destroy the food Charmy worked so hard to make us!
Hey, wait! That's right! It's food!
Yeah, I thought we covered that.
Please, Hofsta!
Stop it! You have to!
Okay.
This meal was a labor of love, and I'm not gonna let it go away!
That'll come out of both ends later.
Feels like my mana's recharging.
Oh yeah, it's flowing out of the party's gnawing arm.
Not so fast, Hofsta!
I'm not letting you eat at all!
Ha!
Bet you want a piece of the action too, don't you buddy?
Obviously!
Alright, I want the rest of you to help them polish it off.
Shouldn't take too long if you all contribute.
But I'm just the transport!
And this is beneath me.
Aaaaaaahhh!
Dude!
Who are you?
And there you go! Good job, fatsos!
And there you go. Good job, fatsoes.
They did it to themselves.
Hey, I meant to tell you.
I feel like that food was different than what you usually cook, and I don't just mean the part where it tried to kill us.
It's kind of hard for me to put into words, but I don't know.
It seemed like the only reason you made it was to build up our mana.
When I eat your food, I can usually taste how much you care about making people happy and stuffed.
I just felt like that was missing this time.
Whoa, that came out really rude. I'm sorry.
Mustard?
Hmm. That's a good point.
In our quest to cook the perfect meal, we forgot the most important thing about being a chef.
Charmy. No, I mean shortcake. One more try!
I'm ready, sir!
Let's do it again!
Here goes!
Give me another!
Lately, I spend most days surrounded by friends.
I'm extremely happy. Possibly happier than I've ever been in my life.
Our battle with the devil is fast approaching, and we have to win.
If we fail, then our happy days will be over.
I thought that last one was pretty good.
Asta.
Huh?
Do you think that I could train with you for a little bit?
Yeah, of course you can!
Hey, Noelle, is it cool if Gordon tags in for you?
Uh, sure.
Give me everything you got!
Okay.
My best?
I didn't plan to do that, but...
I'm sure Asta can handle it.
Alright, here I go.
Poison Curse Magic, Dwelling of the Poison Cloud!
Oh, sorry, Gordon. Are you okay?
As I expected.
I'm no match for you.
I was fighting with all I had.
Maybe I've been getting weaker of late.
When I first met the team, I was truly alone.
But that was largely because I was as sharp as a knife, and I refused to let anyone get close to me.
And now, I've lost my edge.
I love it here with my friends, but I can't remain complacent.
If we're going to defeat the devil, I must regain the strength I had in the past.
And that means I've got no choice but to be alone again.
Lady Mariliona sure is powerful, and she got that way by walking through a strong magic region on her own when she was young.
So I'll cross the forest of poisonous magical beasts near the forest of witches.
I thought it over, and the strong magic region's a little too scary for me, so I'll stick with this.
Things are going well so far.
I knew living my life alone was the best idea.
Okay, time for a break.
I'm a little hungry.
Huh?
That's my food for the whole week!
Wait!
I still can't find my bag.
Maybe I'll go home now.
I've probably been alone long enough.
Uh-oh.
I don't know how to get back.
Eating by yourself isn't as good.
Our meals together were always loud and rowdy, but I had fun.
I really wish my friends were here to help me get through this.
Don't worry, Gordon.
I'll find you something to snack on right away!
We're the GG guys, remember?
Pull yourself together, buddy.
You look so tired, it's scary!
Yeek!
Be tough like me, dude!
I know you can do it!
Forget Magna, I'm gonna kill you!
Great, I'm already starting to go crazy!
Now's my chance.
Let's see how much stronger I've gotten since I left the Black Bulls.
Poison Curse Magic.
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud!
I'll try again.
No good!
My Poison Curse Magic didn't work.
Guess I'm weaker than I thought.
This is the first water I've found in three whole days.
I can live here by myself for a while.
I'll hunt for food alone, sleep alone,
and wash my face alone just like this.
Back at the hideout,
Asta and I would always wash each other's backs.
Some nights I'd drink with Vanessa while we talked about our dreams.
Ghosh let me help take care of his Marie doll every once in a while.
And Luck and I would fight almost to the death.
I must improve myself.
But the thought of being alone has become so painful,
even though that was normal for me before I joined the Black Bulls.
I wonder what my friends are up to tonight.
This is nuts.
We need to get a move on right now.
Come on, there's no time to lose.
Yes, sir!
They'll come looking for me.
I just have to trust them.
You guys, you found me already?
That must be the smaller one's mother.
This is nuts.
We gotta get a move on right now.
Come on, there's no time to lose.
Yes, sir!
Poison curse magic.
How fucking ducks!
It's no use.
My magic isn't affecting these things at all.
This is it.
I'm going to die alone without my friends at my side.
No.
Wait.
The Black Bulls didn't abandon me after all.
I understand now.
I don't need solitude to make me stronger.
No.
I'm strong because of the bond I share with them.
Loneliness is the deadliest poison of all.
And the only antidote that cures it
is the love of my dear friends.
I'm so sorry.
I allowed fear to take over and I wrongfully attacked you and your little one.
As a magic knight who's been tasked with protecting this land,
that's a mistake that can never be forgiven.
You're my allies and fellow residents of the Clover Kingdom.
What's more,
you're my friends too.
Thanks for leading the way.
I see.
The two of you have an immunity to the type of magic that I use.
So that's why my spells didn't do anything.
I'm home.
Oh.
What great friends.
They must have gone out to look for me.
There's no telling what kind of trouble they might be in.
Now it's my turn to go rescue them.
I swear I'll never leave my dear friends behind again.
Totally awesome.
I want all of you to push past your limits by stuffing your faces tonight.
It's your first time's mine.
Hey, boss.
Is it me or is everybody staring at us?
Who cares?
Apparently they're trying to sell off their excess ingredients right now,
which means we can eat as much grub as we want and get 90% off our bill.
Woo!
We won't do two more.
It's our first time.
We forgot to try and run out with us.
Why don't you lose so many sweets?
Because we've provided for us.
And can you learn to make us so much going now?
Helping overnight.
The beenternutught we have to cutall
正解のない道上 そこではきっと一人じゃない
間違いを間違いで終わらせないで 涙を涙で拭わないで
確信があるその心 重げんね
ここならもう一人じゃない
涙を涙で拭わないで